{
    "subject": "resource/Eleventh_Hour_(U.S._TV_series)",
    "predicate": "property/title",
    "object": "Olfactus",
    "human_readable": "The title of the Eleventh Hour episode is 'Olfactus'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9860870242118835,
            "question": "Which episode of Eleventh Hour is titled 'Olfactus'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9841839075088501,
            "question": "What is the title of the Eleventh Hour episode 'Olfactus'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.975129246711731,
            "question": "Does the Eleventh Hour have an episode called 'Olfactus'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9689297080039978,
            "question": "Is 'Olfactus' a popular episode of Eleventh Hour?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9318008422851562,
            "question": "What is the theme of the Eleventh Hour episode 'Olfactus'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9227138161659241,
            "question": "What happens in the Eleventh Hour episode 'Olfactus'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9106809496879578,
            "question": "Who are the main characters in the Eleventh Hour episode 'Olfactus'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8538819551467896,
            "question": "Who directed the Eleventh Hour episode 'Olfactus'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8056607842445374,
            "question": "Where does the Eleventh Hour episode 'Olfactus' take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7545438408851624,
            "question": "What does the title 'Olfactus' refer to?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The title of the Eleventh Hour episode is 'Olfactus'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1648_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where does the Eleventh Hour episode 'Olfactus' take place?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1648_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who directed the Eleventh Hour episode 'Olfactus'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1648_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the main characters in the Eleventh Hour episode 'Olfactus'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1648_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1648_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1648_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1648_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1648_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1648_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1648_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1648_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1648_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1648_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1648_5.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe document mentioning \"Eleventh Hour\" states that there was an episode titled \"Olfactus\", which supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}